<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on jeremy doing things</title>
    <link>https://jeremyrickard.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on jeremy doing things</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 21:53:28 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jeremyrickard.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fun With ACI</title>
      <link>https://jeremyrickard.github.io/post/fun-with-aci/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 21:53:28 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeremyrickard.github.io/post/fun-with-aci/</guid>
      <description>Friday is usually a pretty good day. It&amp;rsquo;s the end of the week and the Azure Containers team has a show and tell with fun demos and people share rants. Today there were also bunch of jokes about clippy which resulted in a bunch of hilarious art from http://textart.io/cowsay/clippy. Such as&amp;hellip;
.@arschles is my hero 🤣 pic.twitter.com/LfYXmde3DE
&amp;mdash; jessie frazelle (@jessfraz) February 9, 2018  Then there were jokes that we needed a bot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Open Service Broker for Azure with PCF Dev</title>
      <link>https://jeremyrickard.github.io/post/osba-pcf-dev/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Feb 2018 08:23:38 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeremyrickard.github.io/post/osba-pcf-dev/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve had the good fortune of working with a great team on Open Service Broker for Azure for the last few months. What&amp;rsquo;s Open Service Broker for Azure (OSBA!) you ask? It&amp;rsquo;s an Open Service Broker API compliant service broker that enables you to easily provision and bind to services like MySQL, SQLDB and CosmosDB in Azure. I was familiar with service brokers from working with Cloud Foundry in the past, so I was really excited to join the Azure team and get a chance to work on bringing the great exeperience developers get using service brokers with CF to Kubernetes with Service Catalog!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Beginnings and a Tale of Two Factors</title>
      <link>https://jeremyrickard.github.io/post/new-beginnings/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 15:50:12 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeremyrickard.github.io/post/new-beginnings/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m wrapping up 2017 with an exciting new job at Microsoft working on the super cool Azure Container Service. I really enjoyed my four years at VMware. I worked on really cool stuff and I worked with some really great people. So why make the change? I had reached a point where I felt like I was ready to do something different and I saw a really intersting job posting on Twitter.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>